Blk. 3, Lot 3, Phase 1, Green Estate. Subd, Brgy. Tiaong, Guiguinto, Bulacan, 3015

🛮 (+63) 9178651511 | 🗷 palaciojanpatrick@gmail.com | 🏕 www.janpatrickpalacio.com | 🖸 janpatrick-dev | 🛅 janpatrickpalacio

Summary.

Software Engineer with 4+ years experience specializing in the frontend development, android mobile application, and game development. Seeking a challenging and rewarding opportunity to use and grow my software engineering skills. Interested in learning new technologies and tools when needed.

Skills_

Programming JavaScript · Python · Java · C#

Front-end ReactJS · HTML5 · CSS3 · SASS

Back-end Node.js · Express · MongoDB · REST API

Technologies Android Studio · Unity

Tools Git · GitHub · Atom · VSCode · Postman · Trello

Languages Filipino · English

Experience

Mad Underground

Mandaluyong, Philippines

SOFTWARE ENGINEER Jan. 2020 - Present

- Develop a mobile application called the "Rabbit Arcade" using Android Studio and Java
- Translate design from Adobe XD to android app using Android Studio
- Develop a game called the "Flying Baby" using Unity C# to be played by the users of the Rabbit Arcade app
- · Create a developer app using Android Studio to be used by the game developers to test and make their game call our scoring endpoint

Anino Inc.Makati, Philippines

SOFTWARE ENGINEER Apr. 2018 - Jan. 2020

- Developed major features on the frontend side: In-game leaderboards, Subscription, Milestone Rewards
- Maintained major features of the project using Unity C#
- Communicated with engineers, designers, producers, and artists on a daily basis

Anino Inc. Makati, Philippines

SOFTWARE ENGINEER INTERN

Aug. 2017 - Apr. 2018

- · Developed new slot machines and features
- Fixed minor bugs and issues
- · Maintained minor features of the project using Unity C#

Education

FEU Institute of Technology (formerly FEU East Asia College)

Manila, Philippines

B.S. IN INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY WITH SPECIALIZATION IN ANIMATION AND GAME DEVELOPMENT

Aug. 2012 - Aug. 2018